To save their souls they must save a kingdom.
Outcast is a action, adventure film directed by Nick Powell.
A mysterious warrior teams up with the daughter and son of a deposed Chinese
Emperor to defeat their cruel brother, who seeks their deaths.
Gallain, played by Nicolas Cage.
Jacob, played by Hayden Christensen.
Lian, played by Liu Yifei.
Shing, played by Andy On Chi-Kit.
Anika, played by Anoja Dias Bolt.
Captain Peng, played by Byron Lawson.
Outcast is a 2014 action film, directed by Nick Powell in his
directorial debut and written by James Dormer.
It stars Nicolas Cage, Hayden Christensen, Liu Yifei, Ji Ke Jun Yi, and Andy On.
The film was slated for release on September 26, 2014, in
China, but was postponed to April 3, 2015.
The film received negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of asia, emperor, crusade, knight, chinese emperor.